

MSc. Lukáš Buňát







🎮 Full-Stack Developer 🖥 Big Data Engineer 🖓 Business Consultant





+420 731 277 533



bunat.cz



bunatl



lukasbunat

Full-Stack Developer with the primary focus on front-end with 4+ years of experience in web/software development and data science. I have an educational background in Computer Science and Business Informatics at many different universities all over the world. I thrive on multicultural teams and enjoy resolving everyday challenges using my analytical thinking and clever solutions.

</>

Technical Skills

	Front-End	React.js 16.12, JavaScript ES6/2017, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, SASS	
Full-Stack	Back-End	AWS services, serverless, Node.js, express.js, apache2, nginx	
technologies	Database	Database MongoDB (Mongoose, Monk), DynamoDB, MySQL, MS SQL Server, JSON lowdb	
_	Other	Yarn, npm, webpack, parcel, babel, postman	
Data Science	Python, R, Tableau, Rapid Miner, Jupyter, Hive, Spark, Hadoop, PySpark, SQL SSIS/SSAS, BI		
Collaboration	GIT, GitHub, JIRA, Trello, Slack, G Suite, MS Teams, Office 365		



Work Experience



Web developer

05/2015 - Present

Freelancing

Prague, Czech Republic

- I consult businesses to digitalize their processes
- I am implementing (web) automatization tools
- Build and maintain business WordPress websites
- I tutor university students in programming
- Implementing additional web apps' functionalities

Video services specialist

05/2018-05/2019

O2 Czech Republic a.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- I helped to deliver the O2TV platform with 500K users
- **O2TV** is a content streaming platform built with ReactJS and supported with other JAVA SE/EE & C applications
- I integrated an audio/video player for Prague's city hall
- I maintain and develop other internal application
- The platform is available on: https://www.o2tv.cz/

Big Data Analyst

10/2017 - 12/2017

Comillas Pontifical University

Madrid, Spain

- Analyzed Spain's power distribution system to discover consumption patterns using clustering techniques
- Analyzed data were stored in **Hadoop**, I processed them with **Spark** (for faster processing) and I used **Hive** for SQL-like interface. Code is written in PySpark
- The findings (visualized in pandas) allowed to pre-assign the necessary resources in each range of time or season

From 2014 to 2019 I had been working as a volunteer tutor at international student club at CTU.



Featured Projects

Portalo

- A portal that links internal and external web apps into a single portal. It comes with a module, that allows to manage employees and their information
- I created project as part of my diploma thesis and distributed it as an open-source project
- Front-end part is written in ReactJS with Ant Design and back-end is hosted on AWS with using GraphQL, Lambda, IAM, DynamoDB, Amplify and Cognito services

Company Business Intelligence Analysis

- I designed and created a database in MS SQL Server based on the structure of the given raw data
- With data pumps I imported raw data from excel, txt, csv and MS Access files, using ETL operations in SQL SSIS
- Based on stored data, I built OLAP cube in SQL SSAS and graphically represented them in Tableau

ReactJS 101 projects

- Differences in Redux, useContent and useReducer
- Comparison GraphQL and fetch
- Deployment npm packages





New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic and passionate about learning new things and technologies



Decisiveness and good decision-making (even uder pressure), leadership



Effective time managment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



Education

Unive	rsity, Year(s) of Study	Field of study, Faculty	Location
STOP OF OR	University of Economics and Business	Information systems and technologies MSc. Graduate (Ing.), exp.06/2021	Prague,
PRAZE	2019 - Present	Faculty of informatics and statistics	Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University	Open Informatics	Prague, Czech Republic
	2019	Faculty of Electrical Engineering	
(SFS)	University of Finance and Administration	Applied Informatics Undergraduate (Bc.)	Prague,
VOI O	2018-2019	Faculty of Economics	Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University	Information Systems and Management	Prague,
	2014–2018	Faculty of Information Technology	Czech Republic
E CHATIOMATE	Kyungpook National University	Exchange studies	Daegu,
STATE OF THE PARTY	2017	College of IT Engineering	South Korea
THE OF HECHTO	Indian Institute of Technology Madras	Exchange studies	Chennai,
E H. Brandara and S. S.	2016	Department of Computer Science	India
THE CHIVERS OF THE PERSON OF T	Delft University of Technology	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland	Delft,
Moccoxui	2016	The ATHENS Programme	Netherlands Netherlands
A	Mayflower College of English	Summer language school	Plymouth, United
	2012		▼ Kingdom



Certificates



CISCO Academy

CCNA 1 (2013)



Autodesk





KFN of UNESCO

Cross Culture Awereness Programme